Ford Foundation records, Office of Communications, Production, Art and Design, Photographs and Negatives, Office Files of Laura Walworth and Dayna Bealy FA1819
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Office Files of Dayna Bealy, 1997-2000; 2; 9.4 Cubic Feet 22 containers
  - 1289C - Annual Report 1999, Kenya Voluntary Women Rehabilitation Center, Assets/Sexual and Reproductive Health, Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 23, Folder 293)
    3 black and white contact sheets, 5 4x6 prints
  - 1289C - Annual Report 1999, Kenya, Voluntary Women Rehabilitation Center, Assets/Sexual and Reproductive Health, Wendy Stone, photographer - negatives (Box 30, Folder 404)
  - 1289D - Annual Report 1999, Kenya, Shangilia Mtoto wa Afrika, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC), Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 24, Folder 294)
    4 black and white contact sheets, 6 8x10 prints, 10 4x6 prints
  - 1289D - Annual Report 1999, Kenya, Shangilia Mtoto wa Afrika, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC), Wendy Stone, photographer - negatives (Box 30, Folder 405)
  - 1289E - Annual Report 1999, Kenya, Community Development Foundation, (Visit from Susan V. Berresford), Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 24, Folder 295)
    1 black and white contact sheet, 3 4x6 prints
  - 1289E - Annual Report 1999, Kenya, Community Development Foundation, (Visit from Susan V. Berresford), Wendy Stone, photographer - negatives (Box 30, Folder 406)
  - 1289F - Annual Report 1999, Kenya, African Conservation Center, Assets/Community Resource Development (CRD), Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 24, Folder 296)
    4 black and white contact sheets, 15 4x6 prints
  - 1289F - Annual Report 1999, Kenya, African Conservation Center, Assets/Community Resource Development (CRD), Wendy Stone, photographer - negatives (Box 30, Folder 407)
  - 1289G - Annual Report 1999, Eastern Africa/Kenya, Mathare Youth Sports Association (MYSA), Assets/Sexual and Reproductive Health, Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 24, Folder 297)
    3 black and white contact sheets, 1 8x10 prints, 7 4x6 prints
  - 1289G - Annual Report 1999, Eastern Africa/Kenya, Mathare Youth Sports Association (MYSA), Assets/Sexual and Reproductive Health, Wendy Stone, photographer - negatives (Box 30, Folder 408)
  - 1289H - Annual Report 1999, Eastern Africa/Kenya Association of NGO of Zanzibar, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Governance and Civil Society (GCS), Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 24, Folder 298)
    7 black and white contact sheets, 7 4x6 prints
  - 1289H - Annual Report 1999, Eastern Africa/Kenya Association of NGO of Zanzibar, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Governance and Civil Society (GCS), Wendy Stone, photographer - negatives (Box 30, Folder 409)
  - 1289I - Kenya, Akina Mama wa Afrika (Women's Leadership Institute), Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Civil Society, Wendy Stone, photographer, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 299)
  - 1289I - Kenya, Akina Mama wa Afrika (Women's Leadership Institute), Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Civil Society, Wendy Stone, photographer - negatives, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 410)
  - 1289J - Kenya, Action for Development (ACFODE), Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Governance, Wendy Stone, photographer, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 300)
    4 black and white contact sheets, 2 8x10 prints, 2 4x6 prints
  - 1289J - Kenya, Action for Development (ACFODE), Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Governance, Wendy Stone, photographer - negatives, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 411)
  - 1289K - Kenya, Human Rights Peace Centre (HURIPEC), Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 301)
    3 contact sheets, 4 4x6 prints
  - 1289K - Kenya, Human Rights Peace Centre (HURIPEC), Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights - negatives, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 412)
  - 1290 - Annual Report 1999, Kentucky Coalition, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Civil Society, John Sommers II/SIPA, photographer (Box 24, Folder 302)
    8 black and white contact sheets, 3 8x10 prints, 4 4x6 prints
  - 1290 - Annual Report 1999, Kentucky Coalition, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Civil Society, John Sommers II/SIPA, photographer - negatives (Box 30, Folder 413)
  - 1291 - Winter 2000, Working Story, Chicago (WSEP, Sisters' Exotic, Elan Coach), Marc PoKempner, photographer (Box 24, Folder 303)
    5 color contact sheets, 3 8x10 prints, 7 5x7 prints
  - 1292 - Annual Report 1999, National Interfaith Hospitality Network, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC)/Religion, Society, and Culture, Philip Greenberg, photographer (Box 24, Folder 304)
    5 black and white contact sheets, 7 black and white 8x10 prints, 8 4x6 prints
  - 1292 - Annual Report 1999, National Interfaith Hospitality Network, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC)/Religion, Society, and Culture, Philip Greenberg, photographer - negatives (Box 30, Folder 414)
  - 1293A - Annual Report 1999, Philippines, Children's Laboratory for Dram in Education Foundation, Assets/Sexual and Reproductive Health (Box 24, Folder 305)
    5 black and white contact sheets, 1 8x10 black and white print, 4 4x6 black and white prints, 2 3x5 color prints
  - 1293A - Annual Report 1999, Philippines, Children's Laboratory for Dram in Education Foundation, Assets/Sexual and Reproductive Health - negatives (Box 30, Folder 415)
  - 1293B - Annual Report 1999, Philippines, Foundation for a Sustainable Society, Assets/Economic Development/Finance and Economic Society (Box 24, Folder 306)
    3 black and white contact prints, 2 4x6 prints
  - 1293B - Annual Report 1999, Philippines, Foundation for a Sustainable Society, Assets/Economic Development/Finance and Economic Society - negatives (Box 30, Folder 416)
  - 1293C - Annual Report 1999, Philippines, Balay Mindanew Foundation, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Governance (Box 24, Folder 307)
    3 black and white contact sheets, 2 8x10 prints, 8 4x6 prints
  - 1293C - Annual Report 1999, Philippines, Balay Mindanew Foundation, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Governance - negatives (Box 30, Folder 417)
  - 1293D - Annual Report 1999, Philippines, Development of Peoples' Foundation, Assets/Sexual and Reproductive Health (Box 24, Folder 308)
  - 1293D - Annual Report 1999, Philippines, Development of Peoples' Foundation, Assets/Sexual and Reproductive Health - negatives (Box 30, Folder 418)
  - 1294B - Annual Report 1999, Vietnam, Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Institute of International Relations, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/International Cooperation (Box 24, Folder 309)
    3 4x6 prints
  - 1294D - Annual Report 1999, Vietnam, Hanoi Agricultural University, RPO, Assets/Environment and Development (Box 24, Folder 310)
  - 1295 - Winter 2000 Women's Issue, Gita Sen, Economist at DAWN in India (shot in Chicago), Nathan Mandell, photographer, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 311)
    990-1002
    67 35mm color slides, 1 internegative
  - 1296 - Winter 2000 Women's Issue, Portraits of Florence Butegwa and Charlotte Bunch, Rutgers University, Martin Dixon, photographer (Box 24, Folder 312)
    black and white photocopies of transparencies
  - 1297A - Annual Report 1999, Indonesia, LP3ES: Institute of Socioeconomic Study, Research and Development, Assets/Environment and Development, Chris Stowers/Panos, photographer (Box 25, Folder 313)
    5 black and white contact sheets, 1 8x10 print, 19 4x6 prints
  - 1297B - Annual Report 1999, Indonesia, Jurnal Perempuan (Women's Journal), Assets/Sexual and Reproductive Health, Chris Stowers/Panos, photographer (Box 25, Folder 314)
    4 black and white contact sheets, 14 4x6 prints
  - 1297C - Annual Report 1999, Indonesia, Studio Audio-Visual, Yogyakarta, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC)/Cultural Preservation, Chris Stowers/Panos, photographer (Box 25, Folder 315)
    6 black and white contact sheets, 1 8x10 print, 7 4x6 prints
  - 1298A - Annual Report 1999, Peru, Human Rights National Coordinator, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights, Morris Carpenter/Panos, photographer (Box 25, Folder 316)
    7 black and white contact sheets, 3 4x6 prints
  - 1298B - Annual Report 1999, Santiago, CCHPS: Chilean Court for AIDS Prevention, Assets/HDRH, Morris Carpenter/Panos, photographer (Box 25, Folder 317)
    17 black and white contact sheets, 13 4x6 prints
  - 1298C - Annual Report 1999, Santiago, LACWHN: Latin American and Caribbean Women's Health Network, Assets/Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH), Morris Carpenter/Panos, photographer (Box 25, Folder 318)
    11 black and white contact sheets, 8 4x6 prints
  - 1298D - Annual Report 1999, Santiago (Buenos Aires), Citizen Power Foundation, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Civil Society, Morris Carpenter/Panos, photographer (Box 25, Folder 319)
    5 black and white contact sheets, 3 4x6 prints
  - 1298E - Annual Report 1999, Santiago (Buenos Aires), Social Science Research Council, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights, Morris Carpenter/Panos, photographer (Box 25, Folder 320)
    20 black and white contact sheets, 1 8x10 print, 3 4x6 prints
  - 1299A - Annual Report 1999, Brazil Office, GAJOP - Legal Assistance Office for Popular Organizations, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Governance, Rhodri Jo/Panos, photographer (Box 25, Folder 321)
    4 black and white contact sheets, 1 8x10 print, 8 4x6 prints
  - 1299B - Annual Report 1999, Brazil, CRIA Holistic Reference Center for Adolescents, Assets/Children, Youth, and Families, Rhodri Jones/Panos, photographer (Box 25, Folder 322)
    9 black and white contact sheets, 1 8x10 prints, 9 4x6 prints
  - 1299C - Annual Report 1999, Brazil, CEERT, Center for the Study of Labor Relations and Inequality in the Workplace, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights, Rhodri Jones/Panos, photographer (Box 25, Folder 323)
    4 black and white contact sheets, 6 4x6 prints
  - 1299D - Annual Report 1999, Brazil, Abrinq Foundation for the Rights of Children, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Civil Society, Rhodri Jones/Panos, photographer (Box 26, Folder 324)
    9 black and white contact sheets, 9 8x10 prints, 16 4x6 prints
  - 1299 - Annual Report 1999 - Brazil, Holistic Reference Center, Assets/Children, Youth, Families, From Brazil Office (Box 26, Folder 325)
    3 8x12 color prints